Guide to the Records of the NYU TV and Media Services Video Recordings RG.38.16.1
New York University Archives
- Series II: Commencement and Founder's Day, 1995-2009; 219016
  - Commencement Videotapes 2007, 219030; 10 videocassettes (Box 40)
  - Commencement Videotapes 2007, 219029; 11 videocassettes (Box 41)
  - Commencement Videotapes 2007, 219028; 8 videocassettes (Box 42)
  - The Churchill School Graduation, 22 Jun 2007; 239059; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 70)
  - Commencement Videotapes 2008, 219027; 12 videocassettes (Box 43)
  - Commencement Videotapes 2008, 219026; 17 videocassettes (Box 44)
  - Commencement Videotapes 2008, 219025; 15 videocassettes (Box 45)
  - Commencement Videotapes 2008, 244086; 0 videocassettes (Box 46)
  - Commencement Videotapes 2008, 226891; 12 videocassettes (Box 63)
  - Commencement 2008, 244402 (Box 83)
  - CAS Winter Baccalaureate, 8 Dec 2008; 243324; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 78)
  - 2008 Steinhardt Doctoral Commencement, 12 May 2008; 238818; 4 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 69)
  - Commencement 2009, 219024; 24 videocassettes (Box 82)
  - Commencement 2009, 244403 (Box 85)
  - Commencement 2009, 244404 (Box 84)
  - NYU Logo: Torch 1831, undated; 219023; 1 videocassettes (betacamsp) (Box 13, Reel Project 61)
    Barcode:31142042272867
  - NYU Logo: Bobcat, undated; 219022; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 13, Reel Project 61)
  - Silver Convocation, undated; 219021; 2 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 13, Reel Project 62)
  - School of Continuing & Professional Studies Ceremonies, undated; 219020; 3 videocassettes (Box 14, Reel Project 69)
  - NYU Logo: Torch Master, undated; 219019; 1 videocassettes (Box 19, Reel Project 61)
  - NYU Logo: Tiffany, undated; 219018; 1 videocassettes (Box 21, Reel Project 61)
  - Unlabelled Commencement, undated; 219017; 2 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 26, Reel Project 82)
  - CAS Winter Baccalaureate, 2010 Dec 6; 245518; 1 videocassettes (dvcam) (Box 90)
  - 1996 Commencement Video Rough Cut, 247020 (Box 94)
  - NYU Commencement 1996: ISO CAM 3 Tape 2, 247021 (Box 94)